geekpadshow.com 2011-11-15

# Privacy Policy – Comedy.com

**We will not sell or give out your email address or other personal information to other companies or websites. We understand that you have put your trust in us by providing this information. We will only use your email address as you agree or allow when you sign-up and/or opt in to receive bulletins from Comedy.com.**

EFFECTIVE DATE: August 6, 2009

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

1.1. Purpose of Policy

Comedy.com, LLC (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of its website located at [http://comedy.com](http://comedy.com/ "Comedy.com") (the “Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

1.2. Notice Concerning Children

We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. In addition, you must be at least 14 years of age in order to set up an account and obtain a user ID with us. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under age 13, or that any registered user is under the age of 14, we will promptly delete that user’s account, including any personal information that might be stored in that user’s account. We also strongly recommend that minors between the ages of 14 and 18 get permission from a parent or guardian before using the Site and before sending any information about themselves over the Internet.

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

2.1. Basic Information We Collect

(a) USER PROFILE INFORMATION. We collect a variety of user-submitted information such as names, ages, and email addresses, in order to establish and authenticate user accounts and to send information and notices to our users regarding the Site and the services we offer. We may also collect descriptive information about users, which can include gender, occupation, employer, education, schools attended, likes, dislikes and other interests, and we may make this information available so that users can find others with similar traits and shared interests.

(b) OTHER USER-PROVIDED INFORMATION. In addition to the foregoing, in operating the Site, we may include registration, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information, as well as information related to the subject matter of the activities requiring registration, of the surveys or of the other online forms. Users may also have the opportunity to post photos and videos, maintain a blog or other form of online journal, and share other materials about themselves, their friends, families and colleagues. Users will have some ability to control access to these user-provided materials, and to prevent the Site from making these materials accessible to all other users.

2.2. Additional Information We Collect

(a) AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) COOKIES. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to the Site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on the Site other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of the Site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

**3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION**

3.1. What Do We Do With Collected Information?

(a) PERSONAL INFORMATION. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to the Site, or to send you additional information about us. We will only permit access to your contact information and other personal information by those other users of the Site for whom you have given your consent to such access. In addition, if you give your permission during the account registration process, we may share your contact information with our business partners or other companies so that they may send you promotional materials.

(b) PROFILE INFORMATION. Your profile information will be displayed to other users of the Site, in order to facilitate the Site’s networking and other interactive features. In addition, users will be able to search for other users, and these searches will be run on the information that is included in our users’ profiles. By registering for the Site, you are agreeing to allow us to include your profile information in our database and to make it publicly available at the Site.

(c) USER-PROVIDED MATERIALS. You will have the ability to control access to your user-provided materials, by requiring that other users must be logged into your profile in order to access these additional materials. You will be able to manage these access controls by logging into your account and changing your privacy settings as necessary.

(d) ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(e) USE OF COOKIES. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your user ID or password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.  To opt out of receiving third-party cookies from our advertisers please visit the [National Advertising Initiative’s website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and follow the instructions they have provided.

(f) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. In addition to disclosures described above, we may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or our parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

(g) SALE OF INFORMATION. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Site. If the Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(h) ACCESS TO INFORMATION. You can review or request changes to the personal information you provided us or to the settings for your user account (including any request that we close your account) at any time by logging in to your account on the Site and changing your preferences on the “My Account” page.

**4\. SECURITY**

The Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, or alteration, and we and our owners, partners and affiliates will have no liability to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

**5\. WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND OUR CONTROL**

5.1. Public Forums

The Site may include interactive forums such as personal web pages, message boards and chat rooms. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and please exercise caution when using any of these public forums to disclose your personal information. We have no control over the use of any personal information disclosed in a public forum, and you are solely responsible for the effects of any such disclosure.

5.2. Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

**6\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES**

6.1. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us at the following email address: [legal@comedy.com](mailto:legal@comedy.com)

6.2. Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
